(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-22T00:03:53.913162",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hey, everybody!
Today, I would like to introduce you
to the one and only entertainer!
Ready, go!
始まった show time
Our showtime has started,
鳴り響く歓声
and the cheers are ringing out.
Let's get up, get up, get up
oh ジャンガジャンガ
Oh, janga-janga,
心躍らせ
making my heart dance.
Let's get up, get up, get up
指を鳴らせば 変わる景色が
When I snap my fingers, the scenery changes.
退屈な街でも ほら ブロードウェイ
Even a boring town becomes Broadway.
今宵の主役は私よ
Tonight's protagonist is me!
One, two, let's go, three, four!
It's my showtime!
Let the show begin 最高の show
Let the show begin, the best show!
楽しみましょう
Let's enjoy it!
一度きりの人生だもん
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, after all.
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
Darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ、勝負よ
For love and work, now, it's a showdown!
One, two, three, four, ha!
Let the show begin!
照らす moon light
Illuminating moonlight,
スポットライトにして
turn it into my spotlight.
Let's get up, get up, get up
oh ラタータッタッタ
Oh, rata-tatta-tta,
軽快なステップで
with light steps.
Let's get up, get up, get up
音を鳴らせば 拍手の渦が
When I make a sound, a whirlpool of applause
轟くスタンディングオベーション
makes a thunderous standing ovation.
今宵の主役に あなたも
Tonight's protagonist is you too!
One, two, let's go, three, four!
It's our showtime!
Let the show begin 最高の show
Let the show begin, the best show!
楽しみましょう
Let's enjoy it!
一度きりの人生だもん
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, after all.
ダーリン ダーリン ダーリン yeah
Darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事も いざ、勝負よ
For love and work, now, it's a showdown!
One, two, three, four, ha!
Let the show begin!
Haha!
Come on, trombone!
Oh... Oh...
Yeah...
Oh... Oh... Oh...
Do we love, everybody, let's go follow me, yeah!
Be scandalous 今にでも
Be scandalous, even now,
Let's get up, get up, get up
Let's do it very, very, very bad!
So beautiful
何度でも
...no matter how many times...
歌おうよ Very very very bad
...let's sing. Very, very, very bad!
Let the show begin あなたも燃え尽きましょう
Let the show begin! You too, let's burn out!
一度きりの人生でしょ Darling darling darling, yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life, right? Darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事もイタズラ心のままに
Love and work, follow your playful heart!
One, two, three, four, ha!
Let the show begin
Let the show begin 最高のShowを楽しみましょう
Let the show begin! Let's enjoy the best show!
一度きりの人生なのだ Darling darling darling, yeah
It's a once-in-a-lifetime life! Darling, darling, darling, yeah!
恋も仕事もイタズラ心のままに
Love and work, follow your playful heart!
One, two, three, four, ha!
This is my show time
This is my showtime...
Ah
I'm breaking な抵抗は罠無理 他の誰でもないの Me
Resisting my breaking point is a trap, none other than me.
君の願いも簡単に叶えたから Look at me
I granted your wish so easily, so look at me.
Be naked
嘘だらけの世界とは Breaker
I am a breaker from this world full of lies.
Wake up
I wish, no filter
ありのままで描いていく Future
Drawing the future just as I am.
見栄もプライドもありのまま アイドル・ライフ
Vanity and pride, just as they are in my idol life.
リスナーだってもう誤魔化せない アイドルにクラック
Even listeners can't be fooled, a crack in the idol.
こだわる My style 幾千の Night 超えていく My life right now
Sticking to my style, overcoming thousands of nights, my life right now...
Judge する My life 見せるだけ 振り向かない
...I'll just show you my judged life and never look back.
魅せてあげる Luxury
I'll show you luxury.
満ちて満ちて溢れ出すの My world
My world overflows, fully filled.
見せつける Ecstasy
Showing off ecstasy.
Don't play, I don't care だから Go my way
Don't play, I don't care, so go my way!
Show me without the filter
Be naked
望むままに Get it
...get it just as you wish.
Be naked
Show me without the filter
Do you understand?
We want this, we must stay 望むままに Get it
We want this, we must stay, get it just as you wish...
脳裏を過る...
Flickering in my mind...
...ミラー・ガールズ
...mirror girls.
We want this あの手の内 だから遠慮はしない
We want this, it's within reach, so I won't hold back.
手が触れた Handle 走り出せ Rambo
My hand touched the steering wheel, drive wild like Rambo!
惑わせる Fantasy
A bewildering fantasy.
満ちて満ちて流されはしないの
Fully filled, I won't be swept away.
幕開ける Final
The curtain rises on the final stage.
I'm okay, I'm okay だから Don't misplay
I'm okay, I'm okay, so don't misplay!
Show me without the filter
Be naked
望むままに Get it
...get it just as you wish.
Be naked
Show me without the filter
自分隠すのは楽だよね
It's easy to hide yourself, isn't it?
周りに合わせてればそれで
If you just fit in with others, then...
とりあえず一人にならずに済むから
...at least you won't end up alone.
本当はもう気づいてる
Honestly, I've already realized...
狭そうにうずいてる
...it's aching tightly.
なのになんで諦めてる
So why have you given up?
もう一度確かめて
Confirm it once more.
始めましょう リアルなShow どこからでも好きにどうぞ
Let's begin the real show, feel free to join from anywhere.
アイドルのハートに Show me without the filter
To an idol's heart, show me without the filter!
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy
Hey, what you need? 大大丈夫さ Hey
Hey, what you need? It's gonna be alright, hey!
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy
そのままで Get it on, get it on
Just as you are, get it on...
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy
Hey, what you need? 大丈夫さ Hey
Hey, what you need? It's gonna be alright, hey!
Hey, what you want? Tell me, please, don't be shy
そのままで Get it on, get it on
Just as you are, get it on...
「ユルサナイ」
"I won't forgive you..."
ゾッとした表情が可愛いね
That shuddering look is cute, isn't it?
君のその身体が欲しいの
I want that body of yours.
Loveit? ナニにラリって
Loveit? What are you high on?
愛 High ハイ
Love, High, High.
可哀想ね 君は悪い子なの？
How pitiful, you're a bad girl, aren't you?
どの子がお好きで 散々に
Which girl do you like? In pieces, in pieces...
色目がお上手で 頭痛気
You're good at making eyes, it's a headache.
君に踊らされちゃって アタシは狂う
Being danced around by you, I'm going crazy.
What is loveit?
君のなかまで
Down to your inside,
骨の髄まで
down to the marrow of your bones.
入れてから 空っぽになる愛のパペット
Insert it, an empty love puppet.
胸が苦しいね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
Your breath is catching, isn't it?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha.
震える声で
With a trembling voice,
ほら囁いて
come on, whisper.
いい子ね 首輪は付けた？
Good boy/girl, did you put on the collar?
君はLoveit
You are Loveit.
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, isn't it?
死体ごっこでしてあげる いって？ アハハ
Let's play dead. Go on, say it? Ahaha.
濡れた君の紅い痕 汚れるまで
Until your wet red scars get dirty,
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけ 死ぬ間際まで
pain, pain, fly away, until the verge of death.
愚かね
How foolish.
間抜けな顔して
Making such a stupid face,
君は悪い子なの？
are you a bad boy/girl?
痛いのがお好きで 散々に
You like pain? In pieces, in pieces...
洗うお口はチャックで
Keep that mouth shut,
なになに？
what is it?
君に踊らされちゃう
Being danced around by you,
君も狂う
you go crazy too.
What is
君のなかまで
Down to your inside,
骨の髄まで
down to the marrow of your bones.
しゃぶりつくせばもう空っぽのパペット
If I suck it all up, you're an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね
Your chest hurts, doesn't it?
息が詰まるのね
Your breath is catching, isn't it?
それが恋と教えてあげる アハハ
I'll teach you that that is love, ahaha.
君はピエロね
You are a clown, aren't you?
愛を囁いて
Whisper your love.
人間のカタチした
Shaped like a human,
君はLoveit
you are Loveit.
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目ね
Love is blind, isn't it?
死体ごっこでしてあげる いって？ アハハ
Let's play dead. Go on, say it? Ahaha.
報いちゃうくらい汚れた血に溺れるまで
Drowning in dirty blood, enough to pay for it,
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
pain, pain, fly away, until your breath stops.
報いちゃうくらい汚れた血に溺れるまで
Drowning in dirty blood, enough to pay for it,
痛いの痛いの飛んでいけ 息が止まるまで
pain, pain, fly away, until your breath stops.
歌ったー！
I sang it!
本当に...
Really...
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026に遊びに来てくれて
thank you so much for coming to play at
本当にありがとうございます！
Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026!
Let's the show begin!
えーと、『ビビデバ』、きっと、『ラヴィット？』 3曲続けて披露させていただきました！
Well, I performed three songs in a row: "Bibideba", "Kitto...", and "Loveit?"!
どうですかー？
How was it?
改めて自己紹介をさせてください
Let me introduce myself once again.
私のもとに おいで！
Come to me!
リオナ・イン・ザ・ステージ！
Riona in the Stage!
プログロウのリーダー、伊咲リオナです！
I'm Isaki Riona, the leader of Proglow!
ぷろぷろー！ よろしくお願いします！
Pro-pro! Pleased to meet you!
はぁ、息切れが... 息切れが酷いんですけど
*Whew*, I'm out of breath... My shortness of breath is terrible,
はい、今日のですね、ハッシュタグはこちら！
but anyway, today's hashtag is right here!
伊咲リオナ生誕祭2026です！
"#Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026"!
たくさん、たくさん、呟いてください！
Please tweet about it a lot, a lot!
私、絶対見に行くのでね
I will definitely go check them out,
みんなが感想とか送ってくれるの、凄く楽しみにしています
so I'm really looking forward to everyone sending their thoughts.
そしてですね、本日
And also, the stage where
ライブパフォーマンスさせていただくステージはこちらです！ どうですか？
I'll be performing live today is this one! How is it?
ショーみたいでさ、めっちゃ良くない？
It's like a show, isn't it really cool?
あとね、伊咲リオナっていうね、名前がたくさん刻まれていたり
Also, the name "Isaki Riona" is engraved all over,
ハートの風船だったり、王冠だったり
and there are heart balloons, crowns,
色んな装飾があって、とってもキラキラしてます！
and all kinds of decorations, so it's really sparkly!
ここでね、踊れることが、今日凄く凄く幸せです
I'm so, so happy to be able to dance here today.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そして、本日のライブのタイトルが「The One and Only」となっております
And the title of today's live is "The One and Only."
こちらの意味は「唯一無二」という意味です
This means "one and only/unique."
このタイトルに恥じないように、全力で、全力でパフォーマンスしていくので
I'll perform with all my might to live up to this title,
どうかこの時間が、あなたの心に何か届けられる
so that this time can deliver something to your heart.
そんな時間になれるように、今日は頑張りたいと思います！
I'll do my best today to make it that kind of moment!
それでは次は、お待ちかねのゲストパートです！
Now, next is the guest part you've been waiting for!
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
Blah blah blah blah blah
I'm a B
La vida, la vida, la vida, la, love, love, love, blah blah blah
ただただのまれるなこんなこと
Don't just get swallowed up by this kind of thing.
触らば可愛いのこのこと
Naively following like a cute one if touched.
高天ヶ原からほら
Look, from Takamagahara,
お通ししてあげる
I will guide you through.
Hi, そう メンヘラ
Hi, yes, mentally unstable.
画面がキュートならメンキラー
If the screen is cute, then I'm a men-killer.
とか貼られたレッテル逝ってるメンタル
This label pasted on me, my mental state is gone.
最恐スマイルで
With my most terrifying smile,
転がしてけBang Bang
roll them over, Bang Bang!
誤魔化してる本心
My true feelings are hidden.
お釈迦にされたらバイバイ
If it gets ruined, then bye-bye.
なんてな
Just kidding.
I'm a B, I'm a B, I am 泡泡よ
I'm a B, I'm a B, I am bubbles.
I'm a B だがディーバ
I'm a B, but a diva.
乱れは厭よ
I hate losing control.
夢見てる少年
Boy who is dreaming,
夢見てる少女へ
to the girl who is dreaming...
Vida la Vida
甘々甘々甘々の
Sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet...
棘
thorns.
ガリガリガリもっと
Grind, grind, grind more.
躍らせてよ
Make me dance!
我を
My self!
センター 誰よりも客寄せるパンダ
Center stage, I'm a panda attracting more guests than anyone.
私は何だ まるで膿んだ自己愛性狂者
What am I? Just a festering, self-loving lunatic.
Am I VIP? Am I chic?
A liar, a liar, Am I chic?
さらいに 奪いに 我愛你 So Love Me
To kidnap, to steal, I love you, so love me.
お留守番ヘイモンスター
Hey monster, house sitting.
My name is ラブラブ
My name is Love-Love.
愛でられたら墓までラフター
If I'm cherished, I'll laugh all the way to the grave.
I'm a leader, all about that
心の中は smooth like butter
My heart inside is smooth like butter.
Touch me したいならほらエンター
If you want to touch me, look, press enter.
¥ Catch me $ ハイピース
¥ Catch me $ High Peace
メシあがる墓場から哀号
Feast on the lamentations from the grave.
狂い心叫ぶ Lifer
A mad, screaming lifer.
生きる姿や魂を今
My living form and my soul...
二つにして愛をバラバラに
...split them into two and tear love apart!
生まれた時の喜びはポーション
The joy of being born is a potion.
さようならでいいな
Saying goodbye is fine.
ダメね
No way.
WachaはMecha Mecha?
Is Wacha messy messy?
楽観なのかね あらら 狂感で共感ね
Is it optimism? Oh my, empathizing through madness.
怪体の正体ね あら
The true identity of the strange body, oh my.
WachaはMecha Mecha?
Is Wacha messy messy?
楽観なのかね あらら 狂感で共感ね
Is it optimism? Oh my, empathizing through madness.
一巻の終わりだね
This is the end of the line.
I'm a VIP I'm a VIP I'm a 我が我がよ
I'm a VIP, I'm a VIP, I'm completely selfish.
I'm a leader I'm a diva 淫らは嫌よ
I'm a leader, I'm a diva, I hate indecency.
夢見てる少年 夢見てる少女へ
To the dreaming boy, to the dreaming girl.
VIPならVIPは 甘々甘々甘々だろ？
If you're a VIP, you're spoiled rotten, right?
そうよさ 子供の頃言われたもんだ
Indeed, I was told when I was a child.
あのヒーローショーの人形の背中にゃ
On the back of that hero show doll...
チャックは付いてないから開くな
...there is no zipper, so don't open it.
バーチャルだ ヒューマンだ 四の五の言うな
Virtual, human, stop arguing about it.
存在はワンダー
Our existence is a wonder.
吠えても 喚いても 死の後はバラバラな
Even if you howl or scream, after death, we're all scattered.
Virtual Blah Blah
Are you ready for...
惚れたら死ぬぞ
If you fall in love, you'll die!
Virtual Blah Blah
Um, I'm a VIP
それじゃ先輩！
Well then, Senpai!
来てくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for coming!
こちらこそありがとうございました！
Thank you so much as well!
一緒に踊れて嬉しかったです！
I was so happy to dance with you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そらりおー！
SoraRio!
そらりおは不滅だよ！
SoraRio is eternal!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
Yeah, that's karma, yeah, get down
Ha-oooh!
Checkmate, I'm a superstar. Stay insane, but you rock with it.
Like 24/7 I'm a hot mess ya love-hate.
Get less boring, oh my god!!
Home run, about to swing my shot
Like a villainous villainess, bring home the jackpot
勇者も悪役も変わらない
Heroes and villains are no different.
派手にブチかまそう
Let's go out with a bang.
Life's just a tightrope, why not stop to fool around?
Chaotic good is peak right now, I can show ya how
Don't get confused, we are not the same
I'm a ruthless dame
No way, no way, way out, way out, yeah
Good versus Evil is so overdone
Let's all kick back and party, just leave it to moi
Whoops, what? Ah
Loosen my lips, loosen my li-li-lips, yeah
That's karma, ta-dah!
Whoops, what? Ah
Loosen my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it
Yeah, that's karma, ta-dah!
Sorry, I'm just better
Sorry, we're go-getters
Ain't my fault we're wicked, stunning, tricky, why you running?
Bet'cha think you're clever, whatever!
Whoa, talk about a 'kumbaya'
フルボッコ罰当てて
Beat 'em up, unleash the punishment.
欲望貪れ
Devour your desires.
アイドル剥ぎ取って We sing
Strip off the idol facade, we sing.
音なら最高潮だわ
If it's sound, we're at our peak.
Boom, boom, that's sweet
Boom, boom, traumatic
Kiss, kiss, kiss, beautiful
この指とまれ
Gather around me.
ハードにハートはハイになって
Get wild, get our hearts high.
弾けて恥じらい捨てちゃいな
Burst out and throw away your shyness.
叫び踊り誇れ
Scream, dance, be proud.
激動的奇想天外
A turbulent, bizarre spectacle.
愛でて頂戴
Shower me with love.
道化のパラダイス
A fool's paradise.
惹かれ合う
Attracted to each other.
狂鳴共鳴
Resonating madness.
Good versus evil, but which one?
Just take a look
That's not any fun.
What's up? With my lips...
Yeah, that's karma, dada-haha-haha!
What's up?
With my lips, I'm about to say some ish, get it.
Yeah, that's karma, dada-haha-haha!
創造から想像
From creation to imagination,
衝動から盲動
from impulse to blind action.
ほら あなた ユーモアに 華麗に 弾けてご覧なさい
Look, with humor, pop beautifully.
ドクドク支配
Pulsing control...
くらい吐き出して
spitting out the dark...
ドクドクファイヤー
Pulsing fire!
Sorry, I'm too clever!
Sorry, I'm a Go-Getter! Am I bad, am I wicked, is it tricky? Why are you learning?
Bitch, you think you're clever,
Whatever.
ドクドクファイヤー
Pulsing fire!
異世界狂いに スイッチングマニアック
Switching maniac into isekai madness,
カラフルに不協和音
a colorful cacophony.
いつだってウガウガにハチャメチャ
Always wild and chaotic,
Welcome to this world's game!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
カリオペ先輩！来てくれてありがとうございました！
Calliope-senpai! Thank you so much for coming!
イェーイ！楽しかった！また歌いましょう！
Yay! That was fun! Let's sing again!
はい、また歌いましょう！
Yes, let's sing again!
また歌いましょう！
Let's sing again!
歌いましょう！
Let's sing!
ちゅちゅっ
Chu chu!
ちゅちゅちゅ
Chu chu chu!
[カルテNo.2222]
[Title: Karte No. 2222]
あー…♡
Ah... ♡
2-2-2 (kyukyu)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2 (doomdoom)
2-2-2 (Doom Doom)
2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2-2 (kyukyu)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2 (burnburn)
2-2-2 (Burn Burn)
chuchu
Chu Chu
open your karte ♡
救助不可能(darling)
Beyond rescue (Darling)
恋の病なの(dirty)
it's lovesickness (Dirty).
どんどん熱を上げていくvirus(loveme)
The virus is raising my fever more and more (Love me).
危険な治療 (twinkle)
A dangerous treatment (Twinkle)
試してみる？ (blink)
want to try it? (Blink)
あく魔で天使の優等生 (heaveninhell)
An angel's model student, yet a devil (Heaven in hell).
ドキドキ動機は純粋 甘い
Pulsing, my motive is pure and sweet.
曖昧乙女心
An ambiguous maiden's heart.
どっちどっち さあ 手の平の迷宮へようこそ
Which way, which way? Welcome to the labyrinth of my palm.
「いい子だね♡」
“Good boy ♡”
カルテNo. 運命の2222 鳴り止まない
Karte No. Fated 2222, it won't stop ringing.
サイレン音が weewoowoowoo
The siren goes wee-woo-wee-woo.
好き？好き？早まる 愛の心電図
Do you love me? Do you? My love electrocardiogram speeds up.
はい お薬をどうぞ ♡
Here is your medicine ♡
tototou ♡
To to to U ♡
2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
2-2-2 (doomdoomdoom)
2-2-2 (Doom Doom Doom)
2-2 (zoom)
2-2-2 (kyukyu)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2 (burnburnburn)
2-2-2 (Burn Burn Burn)
chuchuchu
Chu Chu Chu
open your karte ♡
二十四時間(during)
Twenty-four hours (During)
呼吸困難(dizzy)
difficulty breathing (Dizzy).
真っ赤な薔薇のトゲにキスして(kissme)
Kiss the thorn of a crimson rose (Kiss me).
麻酔みたいな台詞(drinking)
Lines like anesthesia (Drinking),
魔性の Baby face(labyrinth)
a devilish baby face (Labyrinth).
籠で飛び交う青い鳥(try&error)
Bluebirds flying around in a cage (Try & error).
ドクドク毒みたいな支配 笑顔に落下寸前
Pulsing, poison-like control, on the verge of falling into a smile.
チクタクもう時間がない 秘密の正体
Tick-tock, there's no more time, for the secret identity.
「悪い子かも♡」
“Maybe I'm a bad girl ♡”
カルテNo. 運命の2222 追い付けない
Karte No. Fated 2222, you can't catch up.
超スピードで weewoowoowoo
At super speed, wee-woo-wee-woo.
好き？好き？乱れる 愛の心電図
Do you love me? Do you? My love electrocardiogram goes haywire.
もう重症みたいです…
It seems to be already critical...
tootootoo Me ♡
Too too too Me ♡
先生！緊急事態です！
Doctor! It's an emergency!
カルテNo.2222の患者様です！
It's the patient from Karte No. 2222!
見てください！心電図がハートの形になってます！
Look! The electrocardiogram is in the shape of a heart!
もしもーし、聞こえますか？
Hello? Can you hear me?
どこか痛いところはありますか？
Is there anywhere that hurts?
「え？可愛すぎて胸が苦しい？息ができない？」|
“What? It's so cute your chest hurts? You can't breathe?”
「もっと好きになっちゃう注射しましょうね」
“Let's give you an injection to make you love me more.”
「大丈夫ですよー、ずっと私が看病していますからね」
“It's okay, I'll be nursing you the whole time.”
心拍数がどんどん上がっています！
The heart rate is rising more and more!
わたしの声、聞こえますかー？
Can you hear my voice?
「もう大丈夫です！気を失っちゃうかも…」
“It's okay! You might pass out...”
好きなところ言えますかー？
Can you say what you like about me?
「もうこうなったらお医者様の手じゃない」
“If it's come to this, even a doctor can't help you.”
あーあ、だから言ったのに♡
Ah, see, I told you so ♡
そんなに目を見てー！
Don't look into my eyes like that!
カルテNo. さあ選んで 4 Card 裏表ツインテールの Joker
Karte No. Now choose, 4 cards, the double-sided twin-tailed Joker.
Time over そう神様さえ言う通り You're falling
Time over, yes, just as God says, you're falling.
ぎゅっと結んだリボン 誓いましょうティンドン
A tightly tied ribbon, let's make a vow, ding-dong.
運命の警告が連なる暗示
An hint of consecutive fated warnings.
2-2-2
カルテNo. 運命の2222 鳴り止まない
Karte No. Fated 2222, it won't stop ringing.
サイレン音が weewoowoowoo
The siren goes wee-woo-wee-woo.
好き？好き？早まる 愛の心電図
Do you love me? Do you? My love electrocardiogram speeds up.
はい お薬をどうぞ ♡
Here is your medicine ♡
tototou ♡
To to to U ♡
2-2-2 (kyukyu)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2 (doomdoom)
2-2-2 (Doom Doom)
2-2-2 (kyukyu)
2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu)
2-2-2 (zoomzoomzoom)
2-2-2 (Zoom Zoom Zoom)
2-2-2-2 (kyukyukyukyuru)
2-2-2-2 (Kyu Kyu Kyu Kyuru)
chuchu
Chu Chu
open your karte ♡
見上げて あの夜空に
Looking up at that night sky
浮かぶ星達
where stars float
ふっと君の声が
suddenly, your voice...
あの頃輝いてたかな
Was it shining back then?
今になっては
Now that it's over,
ずっとわからないまま
I still don't know.
[オーケストラ]
[Song: Orchestra]
あの時
That time,
君がついた嘘
the lie you told.
問い正せずに
Without asking questions,
泣いたあの坂道
I cried on that slope.
この先
From now on,
君と会えないの
I won't be able to meet you.
離れ離れに
Letting myself
身を任せてた
drift apart.
いつもの後悔が
The usual regrets
風に消えてく
disappear into the wind.
誰にも見せないその姿を
That appearance you show to no one,
もうちょっとだけ見てたかったんだ
I wanted to look at it just a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでる
Time is gently glaring at us.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑いあった声忘ればしないよ
I will never forget our laughing voices.
こんなにも流してた涙も
Even the tears that flowed so much,
語る声もオーケストラ
and our speaking voices, are an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually it arrived, didn't it?
さよならの声忘ればしないよ
I will never forget the voice of farewell.
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
We were supposed to be so close,
今では繋がりなんて
but now, our only connection
あの空だけ
is that sky.
夜空の
Of the night sky,
交換をしよう
let's make an exchange.
馬鹿らしくなって
Feeling ridiculous,
投げた午前3時
I gave up at 3 AM.
この先
From now on,
君と何年も
even if I let myself drift
時の流れに
in the flow of time
身を任せてても
with you for many years...
いつものジョークが
The usual jokes
街に消えてく
disappear into the town.
誰にも見せない僕の姿を
My appearance, which I show to no one,
もうちょっとだけ見せたかったんだ
I wanted to show you just a little longer.
時がそっと睨んでる
Time is gently glaring at us.
この目と目合わせて
Locking our eyes together,
はっきりしたい
I want to make things clear.
もうできないかな
Is it no longer possible?
こんなにももどかしくて辛いのが
This frustrating and painful feeling
音を立てるオーケストラ
is an orchestra making noise.
どこで何をしてるの
Where and what are you doing?
わからないのは
The fact that I don't know
僕のせいなんだね
is because of me, isn't it?
永遠にこんな日がくるなんて
That a day like this would last forever,
神様いたずらなら
if it's God's prank,
呪いたいくらい
I want to curse it.
その手と手繋いで
Holding those hands together,
笑いあった声忘ればしないよ
I will never forget our laughing voices.
こんなにも流してた涙も
Even the tears that flowed so much,
語る声もオーケストラ
and our speaking voices, are an orchestra.
やがて訪れたよね
Eventually it arrived, didn't it?
さよならの声忘ればしないよ
I will never forget the voice of farewell.
触れはしないよ
I won't touch you...
あんなにも近くにいたはずが
Even though we were supposed to be so close,
今では繋がりなんて
But now, the only connection between us...
この空だけ
...is only this sky.
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナ、お誕生日おめでとう！
Riona, Happy Birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
なんと、FGのみんなが来てくれました！ありがとう！
Oh my goodness, everyone from FG is here! Thank you!
やったー！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
はい、ついにね、初めての生誕ライブで。そしてFGでね、こうやってライブできて、凄く嬉しいよ！
Yes, finally, it's my first birthday live concert. And I'm so happy we could perform like this with FG!
祝ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for celebrating with me!
エモかったね
It was so emotional, wasn't it?
エモかった？本当？
Was it emotional? Really?
どうですか？エモかったですか？
How about you guys? Was it emotional?
泣いちゃったよ、リオナちゃん！
I ended up crying, Riona-chan!
泣いちゃった？もらい泣きしそうだった！
You cried? I almost started crying along with you!
みんなでこうやってね、みんなの誕生日ライブがあるかどうか、わかんないんだけど...
I don't know if everyone will get their own birthday live like this, but...
リーダーだけあって、うちらにはないの？
Since you're the leader, do we not get one?
どういうこと！？
What do you mean by that!?
出させてくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for letting us perform!
で、今日は、誕生日プレゼントに、みんなからの超絶可愛い『おめでとう、リオナおめでとう！』っていうプレゼントが欲しいんだけど、いいかな？
So today, for my birthday present, I'd like a super-cute 'Congratulations, congrats Riona!' present from all of you, is that okay?
いいですよ！誕生日なんだから！
Sure! Since it's your birthday, of course!
もらっていいですか、プレゼント？おめでとう！みたいなやつ。
Can I have my present? Like a 'Congratulations!' kind of thing.
じゃあ、せーのって言うから、『リオナおめでとう！』って言ってね。プレゼント、プレゼント！
Okay, when I say 'one, two,' say 'Riona, congratulations!'. It's a present!
プレゼントならしゃーないな。ちゃんと可愛くやれよ！
Well, if it's a present, we have no choice. Make sure to do it cutely!
せーの！
Ready, set...
リオナ！
Riona...
ちょっと待って！男っぽい声が混ざってる！
Wait a minute! There was a manly voice mixed in there!
やり直し！全力で可愛く！
Do it over! Do it cutely with all your might!
でも、ちょっと見本見せてよ。初めての生誕ライブなんだから。
But show us an example first. Since it's your first birthday live.
そうそう、リオナへのお祝いの言葉みたいな。愛が良いよね、愛が。
Yeah, like celebratory words for Riona. Love would be nice, love.
セクシーで可愛くて、愛！じゃあ全身でね、リオナさんの愛の言葉まで。
Sexy, cute, and full of love! Well, show us Riona-san's words of love with your whole body.
いきますよ！３、２、１、はい！
Here we go! 3, 2, 1, go!
今年も、来年も、再来年も！あなたに祝ってもらえますように！
This year, next year, and the year after next! May I have you celebrate with me!
おー！可愛い！
Oh! So cute!
まるで この世界で 二人だけみたいだね
It's as if we're the only two in this world...
なんて 少しだけ 夢をみてしまっただけ
...or maybe I just dreamed a little dream.
つま先に月明かり 花束の香り 指に触れる指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet, fingers touching fingers...
さよなら もう行かなきゃ 何もかも忘れて
Goodbye, I must go now, forgetting everything.
硝子の上を 裸足のまま歩く
I walk barefoot on top of shards of glass.
痛むごとに 血が流れて落ちていく
With every painful step, blood flows and drips away.
お願い その赤い足跡を辿って 会いにきて
Please, follow these red footprints and come to meet me.
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
A goldfish released into a rusty pool.
靴箱の中 隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside the shoe cabinet.
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
Scars left on your withered skin.
迷いに泳いだ迷い子
A lost child swimming in hesitation.
「何処に？」「此処にいるよ」
"Where are you?" "I'm right here."
「何をして？」「ずっと見てるよ」
"What are you doing?" "I'm always watching you."
呼び間違えて満たそう
Let's satisfy ourselves by calling each other's names wrong.
そばにいてよ 遊びに行こうよ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこを見るの
Where are you looking?
ガラスの壁 立ち止まる
I stop at the glass wall.
痛むことに 血が流れて 落ちていく
Blood flows and drips into the pain.
お願い そのかよわい足跡を辿って
Please, follow those fragile footprints...
会いに来て
...and come meet me.
丸くなる
Round and round...
この世界で 二人だけが 残ったね
...in this world, only the two of us remained.
なんて 少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
Just kidding, I just had a little dream.
Ah...
La la la...
Hum...
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Yamate Street in the morning stings my cheeks
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty pack of cigarettes
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Today again I have no space even for my feet
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
And my small room pampers my loneliness
「不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
"Don't love my restless shrieking
未来等見ないで
Don't look to the future
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just live in the moment, something you can be confident in
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name right
身体を触って
Touch my body
必要なのは是だけ認めて」
Acknowledge that this is the only thing you need"
愛してる 独り泣き喚いて
I love you, I'm bawling all alone
夜道を弄れど虚しい
And I wander about the streets at night, but I feel so lifeless
改札の安蛍光灯は
The cheap fluorescent lights at the ticket gates
貴方の影すら落とさない
Don't even cast your shadow
歪んだ無常の時にも
Ah, that warped, distant, and uncertain day...
セヴンスターの香り
...smells like Seven Stars
味わう如く季節を呼び起こす
Tasting them brings me right back to that time of the year
あたしが望んだこと自体
The fact that I wished for anything at all...
矛盾を優に超えて
...goes well beyond contradiction
一番愛しい貴方の声迄
Your voice was more precious to me than anything...
掠れさせて居たのだろう
...did I make that hoarse, too?
誓約を
The covenant...
ドイツ車とパトカー
A German car and a police car...
サイレン 爆音
...sirens, roaring...
現実界 或る浮遊
...the real world, a certain floating.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking...
未来等見ないで
...don't look to the future.
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just live in the moment, something you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name,
身体を触って 必要なのは是だけ認めて
touch my body. All I need is this: acknowledge me.
不穏な悲鳴を愛さないで
Don't love my restless shrieking...
確信出来る現在だけ重ねて
Just live in the moment, something you can be confident in.
あたしの名前をちゃんと呼んで
Call out my name,
身体を触って 必要なのは是だけ認めて
touch my body. All I need is this: acknowledge me.
頬を刺す朝の山手通り
Yamate street in the morning stings my cheeks.
煙草の空き箱を捨てる
I throw away an empty pack of cigarettes.
今日もまた足の踏み場は無い
Today, once again, I have no place to be.
小部屋が孤独を甘やかす
My little room indulges the loneliness I feel.
たららららら
Ta-ra-ra-la-la-la...
ねえ、あんたわかっちゃいない
Hey, you really don't get it.
誰そ彼がお手元の世界に夢中
Everyone's obsessed with the world held in their hands,
化け物の飼い方を学んでる
learning how to tame a monster.
選ばれる為なら舌を売る
You'd sell your own tongue if that would get you chosen,
裏切られた分だけ墓を掘る
digging as many graves as you've been betrayed.
へらへらのおつむがどうにかして
Your brainless head trying its hardest,
うすら寒い言葉ばかりになる
cringe-worthy words overflow.
覚えない顔とバイバイできるなら
If bye-byes can be said to such a facade...
阿修羅にだってなれるわ
...I can turn into Ashura!
逃げるえすけいぷえすけいぷえすけいぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるすてっぷすてっぷすてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Even the devil can be devoured.
騙るすにーくすにーくすにーく 嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるすきっぷすきっぷすきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip... Oh really, who cares?
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって
Might as well bleed them dry.
ねえ、あんたわかっちゃいない
Hey, you really don't get it.
日々の染みを木々に焼べて暖をとり合う
Burning the oozing tidbits of everyday life and basking in its warmth,
義理を訊いた彼の四肢は散り散りになる
he who defied obligation has his four limbs torn apart.
知りもせずに意味を美意識だと崇める
Finding worth in an aesthetic value without comprehending,
擬似餌じみた恤意に御の字だった
couldn't be happier with a compulsion akin to an artificial lure.
愉快な御託のフルコースに
A hilarious full course meal of pontifications...
うわべの面をして可愛がった
...and empty talk showed superficial affection.
くだらない僧と踊るくらいなら
If I have to dance with a good-for-nothing priest...
悪魔と手繋ぐわ
...I'd rather hold the devil's hand!
逃げるえすけいぷえすけいぷえすけいぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるすてっぷすてっぷすてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
阿鼻地獄の果てまでロックオン
Locking on and won't let go until the ends of Avici hell!
騙るすにーくすにーくすにーく 嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるすきっぷすきっぷすきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip... Oh really, who cares?
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
あんた戯言はあの世で言って
Save your silly talk for the afterlife!
逃げるえすけいぷえすけいぷえすけいぷ 仏のまま
Run away, escape, escape, escape as Buddha!
飛べるすてっぷすてっぷすてっぷ 仰せのまま
I can fly, step, step, step as you wish!
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
どーどー閻魔様さえ喰らって
Even the devil can be devoured.
騙るすにーくすにーくすにーく 嵐の中
Cheat, sneak, sneak, sneak in a storm!
跳ねるすきっぷすきっぷすきっぷ あっそ、へのかっぱ
Prance, skip, skip, skip... Oh really, who cares?
アンダスタン アンダスタン
Understand, understand!
いっそ骨の髄までしゃぶって Terrifying!
Might as well bleed them dry.
ねえ、ギャーギャー言っちゃって
Hey, squawking so loudly!
頭を垂れないで！
Don't hang your head!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はぁ、やばい、ちょっと息切れた。
Whew, oh my, I'm a bit out of breath.
お水飲ませてくださいね、すみませんね。
Please let me drink some water, sorry about that.
うーーん...
Mmm...
はぁ、うまい！
Ah, so good!
すみません、ありがとうございます。
Sorry, thank you very much!
お待たせしてすみませんね。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
えっと、先ほどは...
Um, earlier, I performed...
『ジェンルード』と『罪と罰』と...
...'Genrude' and 'Crime and Punishment', and...
『阿修羅ちゃん』をお届けしました！
...'Ashura-chan'!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
この後も、まだまだライブは続きます！
The live concert will still continue after this!
まだ披露してない...
Songs I haven't performed yet...
あんな曲や...
...like that song...
こんな曲があるかもね！
...and this song might be coming up!
なので、チャンネルはそのままで、まだ見ててくれたら嬉しいです！
So please keep the channel right here and stay tuned!
ここでみんなにお知らせをさせてください！
Now, please let me share some announcements with you!
こちらです！
Here they are!
沙咲リオナ誕生日記念...
Isaki Riona's Birthday Celebration...
2026のグッズが出ます！やったー！
...2026 merchandise is coming out! Yay!
では、詳細を...
Now, let's...
見ていきましょう！
...take a closer look!
まずはこちらです！
First is this one!
『RIONA ON THE STAGE』タペストリー！
The 'RIONA ON THE STAGE' Tapestry!
イラストは今回、みんちゅ先生にお願いさせていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Minchu-sensei!
ライブ中のリオナをテーマに描かれたイラストで、
The illustration depicts Riona performing live,
とっても可愛いイラストになっているので、タペストリーでぜひ堪能してください！
and it turned out incredibly cute! Please enjoy it on this tapestry!
2つ目は、こちら！
Second is this one!
リオナとおそろいネックレス！
A matching necklace with Riona!
真ん中には、王冠のデザイン、
The center features a crown design,
周りには沙咲リオナのロゴが入っていますので、
and it's surrounded by Isaki Riona's logo.
あの、シンプルになってますのでね、ぜひリオナとおそろいにしてください！
It has a simple design, so I'd be happy if you matched with me!
次は、こちら！
Next up is this!
リオナのぬいを入れるポーチ！
A pouch to carry Riona's plushie!
リオナっぽさ全開のぬいポーチになってます！
It's a plushie pouch packed with Riona's style!
ぜひ、リオナのぬいを入れてくれたら嬉しいなと思います！
I'd love for you to put my plushie inside!
ぬい以外に使っても大丈夫だよ、ポーチになるよ！
You can also use it for other things, it works as a regular pouch!
そして、そして、最後は、こちら！
And finally, this one!
くしゃみ連発ぬいキーホルダー！
The 'sneeze-spammer' plushie keychain!
今回、描き下ろしイラストの衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになってます！
This is a plushie keychain wearing the newly drawn illustration's outfit!
なんとね、この手の部分をポチッと押すと...
And if you press its hand...
「はっくしゅん！」って言うので、いっぱい押していっぱい浴びてください！
it says 'Achoo!', so please press it a lot to hear my sneezes!
そしたら改めて、フルセットの方を全部見ていきましょう、こちら！
Now, let's take a look at the entire full set together! Here!
盛りだくさん！
So many items!
もちろん、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
Of course, there are also full-set purchase bonuses! Here!
フルセット購入特典の1つ目は...
The first bonus for buying the full set is...
直筆サインと箔押しメッセージ入りのバックステージパス風カードです！
a backstage pass-style card with a hand-written autograph and a foil-stamped message!
こちらもみんちゅ先生のイラストに、全て私がね...
This also features Minchu-sensei's illustration, and I will personally...
1つずつサインさせていただくので、よかったらぜひ買ってみてください！
sign each and every one! So please consider buying it!
2つ目は、特典ボイス！
The second bonus is a special voice clip!
『ライブ前に君と』です！
It's titled 'With you before the live concert'!
ライブ前にこう緊張して、「へへへ」ってなってるリオナを励ますシチュエーションです！
It's a scenario where you encourage Riona when she's super nervous before going on stage!
ぜひ、ボイスの方も聞いてくれると嬉しいです！
I hope you listen to the voice clip too!
こちらのグッズは、21時、9時からカートオープンです！
These goods will be available starting at 9:00 PM (21:00)!
みんなよかったら、ぜひゲットしてください！
I hope you all get them!
そして、大事なお知らせが、2つ目、あります！
And I have a second important announcement!
聞いてください！
Please listen!
ドゥルルルルルル、ジャン！
*Drumroll*... Tada!
沙咲リオナの、初！ソロの新曲が出ます！やったー！
Isaki Riona's very first original solo song is coming out! Yay!
タイトルは『Ring my name』です！
The title is 'Ring my name'!
こちら、私の思いだったり、これから先...
This song reflects my feelings, and how I want to...
どうやってこう進んでいくか、「私は進んでいくぞ」というのが...
...move forward in the future, conveying 'I will march on!'
おしゃれで、優雅に、エレガントに表現された曲となっております！
It's expressed in a stylish, graceful, and elegant way!
こちらセクシーな振り付けもついているので、ぜひ注目してください！
It also features sexy choreography, so I'd be happy if you paid attention to that as well!
この後、このライブが終わった後すぐに、MVも公開されますし、
The music video will be released right after this concert ends,
この後24時からデジタルリリースもあるので、ぜひいっぱい聴いてください！
and it will be digitally released at midnight! Please listen to it a lot!
やっぱりこの後は、新曲やっちゃいますよね！
Of course, I have to perform the new song next!
ということでやっていくんですけど、その前にちょっと語らせてください！
So yes, I'll be performing it, but before that, let me say a few words!
まあね、リオナは、まだまだなことがいっぱいあって、叶えたい夢もいっぱいあります！
You see, there are still so many things I've yet to achieve, and so many dreams I want to fulfill!
何も手にしてない私かもしれませんが、付いてきてくれたあなたと、夢や思い出を作っていきたいです！
I might still be someone who hasn't accomplished much yet, but I want to build dreams and memories with you!
絶対に後悔はさせないんで、これからも付いてきてくれると嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
I promise I won't make you regret it, so I'd be happy if you keep supporting me! Thank you so much!
そしてこの後は、新曲の披露の前に、先輩方のオリ曲を使ったダンスメドレーをお届けします！
And next, before performing the new song, I'll bring you a dance medley featuring original songs by my seniors!
こちら、たくさんのジャンルのダンスを踊る...
In this medley, I'll be dancing to many different genres...
ので、ぜひ見てください！
So please watch it!
いくよ、心の準備できた？
Here we go! Are you ready?
ミュージック、スタート！
Music, start!
A-R-O-U-S-A-L, T-A-N-O-S-H-I-I
My life is so fucking Kawaii
かわいいね
So cute.
死神先生、K-I-L-L-E-R Queen
Shinigami-sensei, K-I-L-L-E-R Queen
セクシーなアサシン
Sexy assassin.
It's the menace of the peace, that's what you wanted, but I forgot
Cause you're dead, bitch. Go dead, jigoku-dera, side to side. RIP...
Cause you're dead, bitch. Go dead, temple of hell, side to side. RIP...
So let me show you the path of the dead, get out of the way, cuz I'm supreme nature
Peace out, 死にたまえ
Peace out, and die
閻魔の地獄絵図
Yama's portrait of hell
doggy doggy god's street
壱 弐 参 飛んで 肆
One, two, three, fly to four
戌神doggy めちゃドープなMC
Inugami Doggy, a pretty dope MC
このエリアきってのかなりハード
This area's quite a hard one
身の丈通りイチコロさ
Hit it right on the spot
噛みついてくる荒くれも
Even the rough ones that come biting
皆まとめて仲間へとアップデート
I'll update them all into my friends
ほら尾っぽ振ってご機嫌に
Look, wag your tail and get in the mood
rock the beat
調子いいね i wanna swing
Good feeling, I wanna swing
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa
混んがらがっても仕様がない ガラスシューズで踊る tonight
Even if it’s chaotic, there’s no other way, dancing in glass shoes tonight
Bibbidi bobbidi boowa
今夜に明日など無い ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
There’s no tomorrow tonight, so those who dance freely win, right?
Ah, ah, yeah
Riona in the house
I'm dressed in lace 甘い嘘はact
I'm dressed in lace, sweet lies are an act
囁くの Want more? 吐息までdanger
Whispering, "Want more?", even my breath is danger
Every step I take 心ごと奪って
Every step I take, stealing your very heart
Velvet shadows call my name 微熱は隠して
Velvet shadows call my name, hiding my slight fever
午前零時
At midnight...
今、Veilが解け
...now, the veil is undone.
I'm breaking into the night まだ夜は醒めやしない
I'm breaking into the night, the night is not over yet
さあ、誰も彼も焦がれるままで
Come on, everyone remains in longing
私を見て
Look at me
Ring my name 響かせるわ 今から watch me fly
Ring my name, I'll make it resonate, now watch me fly
Bloom it now 咲き誇れば 煌めくRiona
Bloom it now, when in full bloom, a sparkling Riona
指先まで優雅に揺れる 鏡越しのマリオネット
Swaying gracefully to the fingertips, a marionette through the mirror
壊れそうに微笑んで
With a fragile smile
Hey hey hey 瞳の奥 falling low
Hey hey hey, deep in my eyes, falling low
唇まで like a ghost
Even my lips are like a ghost
I can't stop 巡る走馬灯
I can't stop, a revolving kaleidoscope
さあ、魅せましょう
Now, let me show you
綺麗な嘘で着飾らないの No, masquerade
No masquerade, I won't dress up in pretty lies
Go ahead, keep deep promise
それならばいっそ Shall we dance? かき混ぜて Rella Rella Rella Rella 頂戴
If so, we might as well... Shall we dance? Stir it up, Rella Rella Rella Rella, give it to me
Flavor fly, no chaser
今さら Bad マーク連打 Bot ばっか やってられねーな
Lately it's just spamming bad marks and bots, I can't stand this
I'm a wonder, can't look away, boy
魅せつけるの 全てを懸けて
I'll show you, putting everything on the line
Are you ready?
Click, click, tap, tap, and keep on posing
Flick, flick, snap, snap, and everybody dancing
微熱の中
In a slight fever,
景色が溶けて
the scenery melts,
まだ夢は醒めない
the dream hasn't faded yet.
To younger me, "you're alright"
名もなきあの頃に
To those nameless days,
「後悔はない」
"I have no regrets."
ring my name 響かせるわ
I'll make my name ring out,
今から watch me rise
from now on, watch me rise.
bloom it now
咲き誇れば
if I bloom in full glory,
煌めく reina
the shining queen.
明け方まで気高く踊る
Dancing nobly until dawn,
琥珀色の masquerade
in an amber masquerade,
壊れそうに舞い乱れ
dancing wildly as if about to break.
viva la reina
Long live the queen!
cantad al alba ya
Sing to the dawn already!
viva la reina
Long live the queen!
cantad al alba ya
Sing to the dawn already!
ring my name 響かせるわ
I'll make my name ring out,
今から watch me rise
from now on, watch me rise.
泡沫の tiara に
Enchanted by
魅せられ
the transient tiara,
ただ憧れ
simply longing,
手を伸ばして
I reach out my hand.
これからも私についてきてください！
Please keep following me from now on!
以上、響咲リオナでした！
That was Isaki Riona!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
響咲リオナ生誕祭2026
お越しいただき、ありがとうございました!!
Isaki Riona Birthday Festival 2026
Thank you so much for coming!!
これからも皆さんとずっと一緒に居たい
貴方の居場所でありたい!!
I want to be with everyone forever
and be a place where you belong!!
お届けしたパフォーマンスが貴方の心に
少しでも何かを残せているといいな
I hope the performance I delivered
leaves something in your heart, even just a little.
本当に本当にありがとう!!
愛を込めて!!
Thank you so, so much!!
With love!!